♪ 'Twas brillig, and the slithy toves ♪
♪ Did gyre and gimble in the wabe; ♪
♪ All mimsy were the borogoves, ♪
♪ And the mome raths outgrabe. ♪
♪ Beware the Jabberwock, my son! ♪
♪ The jaws that bite, the claws that catch! ♪
♪ Beware the Jubjub bird, and shun ♪
♪ The frumious Bandersnatch! ♪
♪ He took his vorpal sword in hand: ♪
♪ Long time the manxome foe he sought— ♪
♪ So rested he by the Tumtum tree, ♪
♪ And stood awhile in thought. ♪
♪ And as in uffish thought he stood, ♪
♪ The Jabberwock, with eyes of flame, ♪
♪ Came whiffling through the tulgey wood, ♪
♪ And burbled as it came! ♪
♪ One, two! One, two! And through and through ♪
♪ The vorpal blade went snicker-snack! ♪
♪ He left it dead, and with its head ♪
♪ He went galumphing back. ♪
♪ Will you walk a little faster?" said a whiting to a snail. ♪
♪ "There's a porpoise close behind us, and he's treading on my tail. ♪
♪ See how eagerly the lobsters and the turtles all advance! ♪
♪ They are waiting on the shingle—will you come and join the dance? ♪
♪ Will you, won't you, will you, won't you, will you join the dance? ♪
♪ Will you, won't you, will you, won't you, won't you join the dance? ♪
♪ "You can really have no notion how delightful it will be ♪
♪ When they take us up and throw us, with the lobsters, out to sea!" ♪
♪ But the snail replied "Too far, too far!" and gave a look askance— ♪
♪ Said he thanked the whiting kindly, but he would not join the dance. ♪
♪ Would not, could not, would not, could not, would not join the dance. ♪
♪ Would not, could not, would not, could not, could not join the dance. ♪
♪ "What matters it how far we go?" his scaly friend replied. ♪
♪ "There is another shore, you know, upon the other side. ♪
♪ The further off from England the nearer is to France— ♪
♪ Then turn not pale, beloved snail, but come and join the dance. ♪
♪ Will you, won't you, will you, won't you, will you join the dance? ♪
♪ Will you, won't you, will you, won't you, won't you join the dance? ♪